http://www.sourcenaturals.com/privacypolicy/

About Us
Get healthy news, tips, and special promotions!
Privacy Policy
At Source Naturals, Inc., we’re committed to protecting your online privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we collect on SourceNaturals.com (including our social media feeds, mobile versions, and any of our related subsites, collectively referred to as the “Site”), how we use the information, whether we share the information with anyone else and if so with whom, and the rights of users of the Site regarding our use of the information, including how users may contact us about this policy.
As our services evolve, we may need to change the ways we use, protect, or share your personal information, and we may therefore from time to time amend this Privacy Policy.  The effective date appears at the end of this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to check our Site frequently to review the Privacy Policy in effect and any changes that may have been made to it.
Information That We Collect
You’re free to explore our Site without providing any personal information about yourself. But in some circumstances, we may request, and you may submit, personal information.
We collect personal information that you provide when you accept an offer: subscribe to our email newsletter; enter contests, sweepstakes, or promotions; respond to surveys or polls, or engage in other activities; post or send us direct messages through our social media feeds; send us email messages through our Contact Us page; or contact our Customer Service Team by phone or email.
By accepting an offer or visiting our Site, you explicitly agree to our collection and use of this data.
We don’t collect personal information about our users’ online activities over time or across third-party websites. Like many websites, our Site doesn’t currently respond to “do not track” signals from browsers. But with most internet browsers, you can take steps to limit tracking; see Cookies on Our Site below for more information about blocking cookies.
Cookies on Our Site
When you use our Site, in addition to information that you may provide, we may collect information by automated means, such as through using technologies like cookies, web server logs, beacons, and JavaScript. A “cookie” is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a site, the cookie is stored on your hard drive in a file specifically designated for cookies.
Like many other sites, we use cookies to obtain certain types of information when you access our Site, our ads, or other content provided by us or by others on our behalf from other sites. Information we gather through cookies may include the date and time of your visits to our Site, the pages viewed, and the time spent at our Site.
We use cookies to:
Personalize your experience;
Collect aggregate information about Site usage by all of our users;
Control the display of ads;
Offer other products, services, and functionalities personalized to you; and
Improve the performance of our Site to provide you with a better user experience.
By continuing to use our Site, you consent to our use of cookies as described. If you don’t consent to our use of cookies, then you may block them through the preferences or user settings in your browser.
In order to use certain services offered on our Site, your browser must accept cookies. If you choose to block our use of cookies, some aspects of our Site may not work properly, you may not be able to access all or part of our Site, and you may not be able to use all of the features available.
For more on cookies and similar technologies, and the browser settings that control them, please visit All About Cookies at www.allaboutcookies.org.
How We Use Your Information
The information we collect from you may be used in one or more of the following ways:
To provide a high level of customer service
To respond to your requests as efficiently and effectively as we can.
To send you emails with information about our products, nutrition, healthy lifestyle choices, promotions, and occasional company updates
To administer or fulfill a marketing promotion, contest, sweepstakes, survey, or other feature of our Site.
To perform data analyses (including anonymization and aggregation of personal information).
To comply with applicable laws and regulations.
How We Protect Your Information
We use a variety of physical, administrative, and technical security measures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. These security measures may include firewall and security technology to maintain the integrity of the Site, password-protected directories and databases to safely store your information, or SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and secure when sent across the internet.
While our security measures meet or exceed industry standards, no data transmission over the internet is 100% secure. Our top priority is to maintain the safety of your personal information, but we can’t guarantee the absolute security of any information you submit to our Site.
Disclosing Personal Information to Third Parties
We don’t sell, rent, or share any personally identifiable information about our visitors with any third party for advertising, marketing, or data analysis purposes.
We may share personal information with our affiliated and service providers who perform services on our behalf, based on our instructions.  We may disclose your personal information with third parties if:
You request or authorize it;
The information is provided to help complete a transaction for you;
The information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property, or safety or the rights, property, or safety of you or others;
The disclosure is done as part of a purchase, transfer, or sale of services or assets (for example, if another party acquires substantially all of our assets, personal information relating to customers, suppliers, and vendors may be one of the transferred assets);
The information is provided to our agents, outside vendors, or service providers to perform functions on our behalf (such as analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing customer service, processing orders, etc.); or,
We believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent harm or financial loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual espionage, cybersecurity events, or other fraudulent or illegal activity.
Keeping Personal Information
How long we keep information that we collect about you depends on the type of information. We retain aggregate information generated by cookies and other tracking technologies for a reasonable period of time from the date that such information was created.
We retain personal information that you provide to us where we have an ongoing, legitimate business need to do so (for example, as long as you’re subscribed to our services, or as needed to comply with our legal obligations or resolve disputes).
If you’ve subscribed to our emails, entered a contest or sweepstakes, participated in a social media initiative, or responded to a promotional offer, we retain the information you provided for a reasonable period of time from the date you last expressed interest in our content, products, or services (such as when you last opened an email from us).
When we have no ongoing need to retain personal information, we securely delete or anonymize it. We will delete your information sooner if you so request by contacting us as described in “How to Contact Us and Opt Out” below.
Links to Other Websites
Our Site may contain links to third-party websites whose privacy practices are different from ours. Such links are not an endorsement of these sites, their content, their owners, or their practices. We are not responsible for these sites and have no control over the information that they may collect. Users should consult these sites’ privacy policies for details about how they collect and use any information that you submit to them.
Children Under 18
Our Site is not intended for or targeted at children, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from anyone under the age of 18. If you’re under 18, you may use this Site only with the involvement of your parent or guardian. If you believe that we’ve collected information about a child under 18, please contact us here so that we may delete it.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or its implementation on our Site, or you want to opt out of any subscriptions, please follow the link at the bottom of any email you receive from us. You may also contact us at
Source Naturals, Inc.
PO Box 2118
Santa Cruz, CA 95062
(800) 815-2333 or (831) 438-1144 (local), Mon-Fri 8am-4:30pm Pacific
Contact Us Page
Specific privacy and data retention requests can be made to the Webmaster using the form on our Contact Us page at www.sourcenaturals.com/contact_us
Territorial Use Restrictions, Jurisdiction, and European Union Compliance
This Site is controlled and operated by Source Naturals, Inc. in the United States. We make no representation that this Privacy Policy complies with any applicable laws outside the US; users who choose to access our Site and subscribe to our emails from locations outside the US do so at their own initiative and risk.
This Privacy Policy and other policies on this Site shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California. All claims, disputes, and lawsuits arising out of or in connection with this Privacy Policy shall be resolved or adjudicated in Santa Cruz County, California.
Source Naturals, Inc. doesn’t engage in directed marketing efforts outside the United States and doesn’t maintain any sales, representatives, or other office or presence outside the United States. We do respond to inquiries that originate outside the United States, including from the European Union, and we’ve taken steps to comply with the requirements of the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), but Source Naturals, Inc. is not required to register with any data protection authority.
Last updated August 24, 2018
About Source Naturals®
Where to Buy
SystemiCare®
Contact Us
Site Map
Solutions for Nutrition
Sleep
©Source Naturals, Inc. 2016 All Rights Reserved.
